{ Matheus Seabra }

>>> SOFTWARE ENGINEER



PERSONAL SUMMARY

I'm a full-stack software engineer with over 5 years building web and mobile applications from client to server. Over the years had the privilege of working with spetacular agile software engineering teams in industries ranging from Edtech, Fintech and Enterprise.

GET IN TOUCH

Portfolio: matheuseabra.me

Github: github.com/matheuseabra

Email: matheus vieira coelho@gmail.com

Phone: +55 27 99284-3758

Vitória ES - Brazil

TECHNOLOGIES & TOOLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- · React, Vue.js
- React Native
- Node.js
- Python
- GraphQL
- PostgresSQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- JWT, Auth0
- Docker
- Linux
- Amazon Web Services
- CircleCI
- Git
- GitHub

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

FineTune Learning | 2019 - Present

Working with the innovation team, collaborating with PO's, Designers and QA engineers helping to deliver the vision for their main product FineTune Writing, scaling the product up to thousands of students in the U.S.

Frontend Developer

Vibe | 2018 - 2019

Responsible for defining the overall client-side architecture for the applications projects and mentoring junior developers to use the appropriate design patterns, development practices and processes. The team was able to deliver features faster due to the processes applied.

Frontend Developer

Acception | 2017 - 2018

Led a successful refactor of the UI layout and client-side legacy architecture from jQuery to a modern frontend architecture built with React. Clients were delighted with the end result.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Rocketseat

GoStack Bootcamp | 2020

Treehouse

Fullstack JavaScript Development | 2017

Federal University of Pará

BS Information Systems | 2013 - 2017